Notes:

Slogan: Fly Further, Faster with Jet...Set...Go!



rgb(0, 0, 0); black
rgb(20, 33, 61) dark blue
rgb(252, 163, 17) yellow
rgb(229, 229, 229) light gray
rgb(255, 255, 255) white



TODO: 
Show what is selected
The ability to select multiple
Show what you have saved
Build a larger database to show off what a user's view would be
Allow for deletion of saved flights
Make a demo while commenting what is happening and put it on youtube